I can do that?
No. no. I've already been
to hell and back!
I won't let you take this from me.
I won't die!
Huh?
Did increasing my strength stat
make that much of a difference?
Doesn't matter.
it's still got me outclassed.
My attacks aren't working!
How am I supposed to win?
I can't do this alone.
No party. no healer.
I only packed water and food.
I'm screwed.
I should've brought some
kind of magic weapon!
Wait! Open inventory!
How'd Mister Kim's sword
even get in there?
I remember him saying
he paid 3 million for it.
Way outside my budget.
that's for sure.
But since I have it. I should use it.
Huh? Hey. the pain's fading.
Now that I'm armed. you're not scary!
What? It's stuck!
Come on! Come out!
Ah!
Guess you're called
"steel-fanged" for a reason.
But I just got this sword so!
Chew on something else!
I've gotta admit.
Compared to those behemoths.
you mutts are nothing.
Hmm?
Whoa. I'm at level two.
Completing daily quests
never changed that.
Guess it's triggered by real combat which
explains why my wounds suddenly healed.
And the bonus for leveling up is all my
stats go up by one. which is cool. I guess?
If I get five points each time.
and daily quests only net me three.
fighting definitely seems
like the way to go.
I wonder if one point really makes
a noticeable difference in power.
'Cause there are values for
perception and intelligence. too.
But strength's the easiest to gauge.
My body feels much lighter than before.
and that's with just 32 points.
Based on what I've learned.
I'm willing to bet that I have
unlimited potential now.
My level and abilities
will just keep going up.
If that's true.
then I can get stronger.
Well. I've only killed five magic beasts.
so maybe I'm getting ahead of myself.
Let me see here.
Did you drop any essence stones?
Huh? Oh. okay. guess I get
fangs and stuff instead.
This strange system I'm caught up in.
Its rules follow game logic
as opposed to real world logic.
So. the beasts in this dungeon will be
different from the ones inside the gates.
Oh. I have access to a shop.
Can I buy?
Beginners are locked out.
Figures. I'll sell. then.
Twenty gold?
And no way of telling how much
that's actually worth.
Considering I still have a pulse.
I think it's an E-Rank dungeon.
so 20's probably
not all that much. really.
Okay. what's next?
To get outta this place.
I gotta defeat the boss.
Teleporting is out
since I don't have any stones.
And I can't waste time
looking for them either.
I don't have enough food
to stay that long.
E-Rank dungeon or not. I don't think
I can beat a boss all on my own.
But maybe my chances would be
better if I leveled up.
I'm sure they would. though I
could easily die in the process.
I shouldn't be afraid.
After all. I've already died once!
I am not going down easy.
And I expect a good fight
from you. too.
'Cause. if I kill you too fast.
I just know that I'm gonna feel bad.
You're qualified to be
a hunter. Mister Sung.
Now we can pay for mom's treatment!
I wish I had another chance.
Let's go.
Come at me with all you've got!
Fight as hard as we can.
till the very end!
If it means I'll get stronger.
I'll follow these rules. no
matter how ridiculous they are!
-Oh!
-Man. that can't be good.
The Association needs
to fix this. stat.
This blade is pretty much spent.
At the end of the day.
every weapon is disposable.
Even the ones with outrageous price tags
are ruined after a handful of dungeon runs.
but I know this sword
is why I'm still here.
That battle scored me 34 wolf fangs.
two worn daggers. a traveler's cloak.
And look at that. a safe escape
via my shiny. new teleportation stone.
Should I call it and leave?
Mm.
What if I never get the chance
to level up this easily again?
This dungeon might vanish the instant
I teleport out of here. I don't know.
Maybe it's like a limited-time event.
which makes the disappearing
thing all the more likely.
Ultimately. I'm being played
by someone or something.
On the Buddha's palm.
doing my little dance.
Do I keep going forward.
or head back?
Yes? Joohee Lee speaking.
Oh. Of course. I remember. sir.
I'm sorry I turned you down
the other day.
Huh?
There was a dungeon break
at that gate?
That's not too far!
If I'd accepted his offer...
We've been reaching out to
every available hunter we can.
but there's a major shortage
of healers. Miss Lee.
I'll be right there.
Each time my level goes up. killing
magic beasts gets a little easier for me.
Their labels changed colors. too.
I think white means
they're relatively weak.
Orange is about equal to me.
and red. red means trouble.
The Lycans were red
when I first fought them.
Now. they're all white.
That's just how much
stronger I've gotten.
And yet. I'm still hesitant to take
on whatever's waiting down there.
My perception stat
got a significant boost.
so I can sense it.
There's something powerful
beneath me.
and it's giving me chills.
I doubt I can level up any more here.
And this sword's a few swipes
away from breaking.
Is it just me. or does this thing
have more steps than it used to?
How is this place Hapjeong Station?
Huh?
It's fast!
The sword!
What color's the name?
C'mon. please. be white.
Please. be white. Please. be white.
I leveled up fourteen times.
so surely you have to be...
Crap.
"King of the Swamp" and boss
of the dungeon. yeah?
Even before it broke. no way this
sword could pierce those scales.
And fist fighting's definitely out.
Between its speed and how
it throws its weight around.
getting through its defense
is gonna be tricky!
I mean. what can I do
against armor this thick?
One clean hit on me. and I'm dead.
The little strength I
gained was huge for me.
But it. it's still not enough.
How much stronger do I need to get
before I'm finally able to escape
my past as a laughing stock?
"The Weakest Hunter of All Mankind?"
Yeah. I hear that's what
they've been calling you.
Oh. I see.
They're adults. yet they act like
such childish jerks sometimes.
Work hard and prove them
all wrong. I know you can.
Right. I will.
Thanks. Mister Song.
I'm weak. so I get a crappy nickname.
I'm weak. so no one believes in me.
I hate how worthless I am.
I want strength!
Overwhelming power
brings people to their knees.
The strong go into every
situation with an advantage.
while the weak quiver in fear
or stand around helplessly.
The weak get looked down on.
Doesn't matter how smart.
creative. or kind they are!
The weak always lose!
I always lose.
My kindness never saved me. No.
What I need now is true strength.
And I am not gonna
give up until I get it!
Just watch me!
I swear it.
I'll get stronger
if it's the last thing I do!
I'm not done yet!
Compared to that thing.
compared to the terror I felt that day!
This is nothing!
Ah!
I put all of my
ability points into strength!
With the power I have...
I know I can kill you
right here and now!
So die!
Even if it's just a bit.
"The Weakest Hunter
of all Mankind" got stronger.
Well. at least I bagged a nice prize.
Though I'm kinda shocked it's made
from the snake's fang instead of its bone.
It has double the attack power
of Mister Kim's sword.
plus. paralysis and drain effects!
And what do we have here?
Seems too scary to use.
but I'll still hang on to it.
Huh?
I beat the dungeon.
It's like a ghost town.
What time is it?
Hey. you!
No civilians beyond this point.
Did you not listen to the broadcast?
What broadcast?
Look. kid. This isn't a joke.
Huh? Wait. Are you a hunter?
Yes. sir. That's correct.
I apologize for the confusion.
Allow me to escort you.
Right this way.
Oh. okay.
Sounds like something bad happened.
Of course. a dungeon break.
How many magic beasts
are still wreaking havoc. sir?
Most have been dealt with
since it's nearing the end.
Only one left now.
and it's a big one.
My enhanced perception
told me as much.
It's over there.
The boss is alive and kicking.
No pictures. please!
You should be evacuating!
How much longer will this take?
What if the fight continues to
escalate and gets even worse?
Come on. healers!
Focus all of your energy
on supporting the tank!
That's what we're doing!
Can't you tell?
Are none of you damage
dealers taking this seriously?
I don't think you've put
a single crack in this rock!
Its defense is insane at
least against physical attacks.
and we're short on mages.
so what can we do?
Make way! Hunter coming through!
This crew looks thrown-together
last-minute. Very out of sync.
Low ranks. too.
I see eight E-Rank hunters and two D.
One of the D's is a tank. which
is why this battle has dragged on
longer than it should.
As for healers.
we've got two D and a B.
Hey. you gonna help or not?
You're the highest ranked healer we have.
and we clearly need some support magic!
Don't just stand there. lady!
Right! I'm sorry!
Stay alert and you won't have to be!
One week later. and she's
still shaken up about it.
Can't blame her. though.
I am. too.
No.
It's a D-Rank boss.
And I just tore through
a much tougher beast's throat!
We'll be wiped out at this rate!
Why'd no one recruit
higher-ranked hunters for this?
If I breach its defenses. that's it.
They win!
Can I pierce it with one strike?
Let's see!
Look! Its barrier's down!
Now's our chance!
You guys. we actually did it!
Our attacks barely scratched it. then
suddenly its shield was obliterated.
No one goes from doing zero to a
hundred damage. so it wasn't us.
Who or what was it?
A boss-level golem
that withstood the attacks
of over ten hunters. completely unfazed.
got done in by a piece of junk?
-Excuse me. sir.
-Yes.
Did you happen to see
who threw that broken sword?
Yeah. it was that
straggler hunter there. Wait...
What incredible power.
How high is that guy ranked?
I didn't think a single attack
would work.
Best guess is. that golem's
stamina was already low. Hmm.
Jinwoo. was that you?